https://www.webucator.com/about-us/privacy-policy.cfm

HomeCourse CatalogTraining Delivery MethodsLive Online ClassesPrivate ClassesSelf-Paced TrainingEnterprise TrainingAll Training OptionsPurchase CoursewareAbout Us Sign In Contact Us  1-877-932-8228
© 2020 Webucator, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
Courses
Search
Live Online ClassesPrivate ClassesSelf-Paced TrainingEnterprise TrainingAll Training OptionsPurchase CoursewareAbout Us
About UsHomeAbout UsPrivacy Policy
What information do
we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an
order or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate,
you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone
number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site
anonymously.
What do we use your
information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the
following ways:
To personalize your experience (your information
helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our website (we continually
strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback
we receive from you)
To improve customer service (your
information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service
requests and support needs)
To process transactions (Your information,
whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given
to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other
than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service
requested.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey
or other site feature
To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order
processing, will only be used to send you information and updates
pertaining to your order.
If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you
will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or
service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to
unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe
instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect
your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your
personal information when you place an order:
We offer the use of a secure server. All
supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer
(SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database
only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such
systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information
(credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on
our servers.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers
to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that
enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and
capture and remember certain information).
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your
shopping cart.
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you
each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via
your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some
of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders
by contacting customer service.
Do we disclose any
information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your
personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third
parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or
servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information
confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is
appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours
or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor
information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or
other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party
products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and
independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability
for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to
protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Online Privacy Policy
Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through
our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our
Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on
this page.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us
using the information below:
Address
Webucator, Inc.
